

Julian David Sierra Guarnizo

Software developer with Scrum Master certification, knowledge and experience in team lead, Object Oriented programming, .NET, Development of web application with ASP.NET, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Jquery, Angular and React js use of tools Visual Studio 2008, 2010, 2012, 2017 and 2019, Framework 4 and 4.5, Services Windows Communication Foundation, Linq, ADO.net, Entity Framework, Database SQL Server and administration of internet information services.

Development of mobile application with Xamarin forms, knowledge of Api management and creation of azure functions with node js.

Administration of tools for version control Team foundation server, Git, and Azure Devops.

EDUCATION

System Engineering *Universidad Cooperativa de Colombia*2011 - 2015

Scrum Master Scrum Study 2017

Fundament C#, VB, MVC and Microsoft Azure in Web Sites Microsoft Virtual Academy 2015 **Aux. Software Development**

Sena

2008 - 2010

Scrum Fundamentals Scrum Study 2017

Soft Skills

SOIT SKIIIS			
Creative	Agility	TeamWork	
Assertive Communication	Team leadership		

Lenguages and Technologies

ASP.NET	C#	SQL Server
WCF	Web Api	Entity Framework
CSS	jquery	Html
JavaScript	Angular	Xamarin
IIS	Api Management	Git
Azure Functios	Node Js	TDD

Professional Experience

Perficient Latin America.

May. 2021 - Present

Functions

- Implement the new features applying the SOLID principles, pattern design with different technologies, build CD and CI and support to the team members developer in different task.

Accenture.

January. 2017 - 2021

Functions

- Build and maintain of website for e-commerce, on the .Net platform with the database SQL Server
- SME for the tower .Net, requirements analysis, integration analyst and versioning management
- Build of mobile app with Xamarin forms, Api management and azure functions
- Architecture definition
- Builds a business requirement

ControlBox Corp.

December. 2015 - January 2017

Functions

- Development and maintain of app on the ASP.Net using JS, Jquery, HTML, VB.Net and C# with database SQL Server
- Requirement analyst for new features with use the good practices and new technologies
- Build a WCF for integrate with external service

IBM Corp.

June 2015 - December 2015

Functions

Components build of high engineering and help in the maintain the different apps

LANGUAGE

o English: Intermediate o Spanish: Native

INTERESTS

- ✓ Scrum
- ✓ Safe✓ Design patterns

Personal Reference

Juan Corchuelo Armando Quiñones

Phone: +57 301 7874861 Phone: +57 302 2626917

Contact

E-mail: jjsierra.1993@gmail.com

Phone: +57 310 3105119